propertyfinder.qa 2017-06-30

# propertyfinder.qa - Qatar's #1 property site

**Our commitment to you**

Propertyfinder.qa  respects your privacy and is committed to protecting personal information collected from you through our website. This privacy policy governs the way we collect and use information, and by using the services on our website ('Services') you agree to be bound by this policy. All references within this policy to 'we/us/our' refer to propertyfinder.qa.

This Privacy Policy is in addition to any other terms and conditions applicable to the web site. Specific privacy terms contained in any documents made available by us should be read together with this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. You should review this Privacy Policy periodically so that you are updated on any changes. 

We do not make any representations about third party web sites that may be linked to the web site.

**Information we collect**

When you use the Services you will have the option to provide us with personal information, such as your email address, so that we may keep you informed. We use this to provide the Services.

When visiting our website, we may place one or more cookies (a small file that is stored by your browser to recognise you and store your preferences) on your computer. This helps us to improve our Services by personalising information you may want. You may adjust the settings on your browser to refuse cookies but some of the Services may not work if you do so.

In order to provide you with services, answer your enquiries, deal with your requests or improve the services we offer you, we may collect and process the following personal information about you:

  * Information, such as your name, email and other contact details (including information that you provide by filling in forms on the web site). 
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them. 

**How do we use your personal information?**

We may use personal information in the following ways:

  * To ensure that content from the web site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 
  * To provide you with service information, products or services that you request from us. 
  * We may (1) use personal information held about you to provide you with information about offers, promotions, goods or services, which we believe may be of interest to you and (2) share your information with our service providers and other third parties so that they can contact you directly about their offers, promotions, goods or services. If we do use your personal information in these ways, we will always give you the opportunity to request that your information not be used for further direct marketing in the future. 
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so. 
  * To notify you about changes to our service and remind you of your password and username. 

**Communicating with you**

If you prefer not to receive emails about our Services, you may opt out of such communications by following the instructions at the bottom of any of our emails.

**Third parties**

We use third parties to serve advertisements on our website and these third parties may use cookies or other means to help measure the effectiveness of their advertisements. Our website may also include links to other unrelated websites and/or contact forms to other unrelated parties which may collect personal information. Our privacy policy does not extend to these third parties or other websites and we recommend that users refer directly to these parties regarding their privacy policies before supplying personal details to these companies.
